<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <!-- <function name="write" model="ir.model.data">
        <function name="search" model="ir.model.data">
            <value eval="[('module', '=', 'tds'), ('name', 'in', ['tds.fillup_it_rem_declaration_mail'])]"/>
        </function>
        <value eval="{'noupdate': False}"/>
    </function> -->
    <data noupdate="0">

   
        
        <record id="user_tds_fillup_mail_template" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">IT Declaration Reminder Mail</field>
            <field name="email_from">tendrils@csm.tech</field>
            <field name="subject">IT Declaration Reminder Mail :: ${ctx['name']}</field>
            <field name="email_to">${ctx['email']}</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="hr_contract.model_hr_contract" />
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="False" />
            <field name="body_html">
                <![CDATA[
                     <table border="0">
                        <tr>
                            <td>
                                <div style="margin-left: 1.2rem;margin-bottom:1em;">
                                    <h5 style="font-weight: 400;margin-bottom: 0;font-size: 16px;color:#676767;">
                                        <span style="color:rgb(22, 123, 158);font-size: 16px;margin-right: 2px;font-weight: 600;">Dear</span>
                                           ${ctx['name']},
                                    </h5>
                                    <p style="color: #676767;line-height: 145%;margin: 10px 0 0 0;font-size: 16px;">
                                    For the purpose of calculation of Income Tax Liability for the year ${ctx['fy']} on your salary income, you are required to choose the option of taxation.<br/><br/>
                                    This is available in Tendrils v6 under the tab ‘IT Declaration’ >  ‘My Tax’ > ‘My declaration’ > 'Create'.<br/><br/>

                                    First, you will be prompted to choose based on which of the following two options you want your income tax liability to be calculated:<br/><br/>


                                     a)Based on the tax slab where total income is effectively tax free up to an amount of Rs.7 lakh. Section 115BAC (New Regime)<br/><br/>
                                     b)Based on the tax slab where total income is tax free up to an amount of Rs.2.5 lakh. (Old regime)<br/><br/>

                                    In case you choose ‘Option (b)’,then you’ll be prompted to fill up your various investment options.<br/>

                                    As per existing income tax rule, if an employee does not choose any option, the default option will be option (a).<br/>
                                    For making it easy, in case of the employees who were on the rolls in the previous year, the data of previous year has been imported as tentative data for current year.<br/>


                                    You are free to revise all the items and add new items. However, in case you choose not to revise, it will be assumed that you agree to the data that appears for the current year.<br/>


                                    Please feel free to contact Finance Department in case you have any queries.<br/></p>
                                    <p style="color: #676767;line-height: 145%;margin: 10px 0 0 0;font-size: 16px;">Please fill up the form in Tendrils before ${ctx['date']}.</p><br/>
                                </div>
                            </td>
                        </tr>
                    </table>
                    ]]>
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>