<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="0">
        <record id="employee_email_template" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Onboard e-mail template</field>
            <field name="email_from">${ctx['email_from']|safe}</field>
            <field name="subject">Welcome to the CSM Pre-Onboarding!</field>
            <field name="email_to">${object.email|safe}</field>
            <field name="email_cc">${ctx['email_cc']|safe}</field>
            <field name="lang">${object.lang}</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="kw_onboarding_process.model_kwonboard_enrollment"/>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="False"/>
            <field name="body_html" >
            <![CDATA[
                <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%" >
                    <!-- CONTENT -->
                    <tr>
                        <td align="center" style="min-width: 590px;">
                            <table border="0" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" style="min-width: 590px; background-color: white; padding: 0px 8px 0px 0px; border-collapse:separate;">
                                <tbody>
                                <tr>
                                <td valign="top" style="font-size: 13px;">
                                    <div>
                                        <h5 style="color:#676767;font-size: 18px;margin: 0 0 0 0 ;font-weight: 400;">
                                            Welcome to ${object.company_id.name}
                                        </h5>
                                        <br/>
                                        Dear <strong>${object.name},</strong>
                                        <br/>
                                        <p>Welcome to the  Family,</p>
                                        <p>Thank you for accepting the offer and choosing to join  Family.</p>
                                        <p>I am your Onboarding Advisor, welcome you to  Onboarding Program. I will enable your transition
                                        into  and will support you in your onboarding journey.</p>

                                        <p><strong>Please go through this mail carefully, as it has important information regarding your joining.</strong></p>

                                        <p>You need to fill in your personal details and upload the required documents under the respective sections in the CSM Onboarding link below, 
                                            % if object.profile_submit_date:
                                                <strong>by ${object.profile_submit_date.strftime('%d-%b-%Y')}</strong>
                                          % else:
                                                <strong>NA</strong>
                                          % endif
                                        .</p>
                                        <div style="margin: 16px 0px 16px 0px;">
                                            <a href=" ${website_url}/onboarding/?txtMobNum=${object.mobile}" style="background-color: #875A7B; padding: 8px 16px 8px 16px; text-decoration: none; color: #fff; border-radius: 5px; font-size:16px;" target="new">
                                                Click Here
                                            </a>
                                        </div>

                                        <p>It is vital for you to review your information carefully and highlight any discrepancies to me.</p>
                                        <div style="">
                                            1. <strong>Personal Details</strong> :
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>Profile details should be filled up based on the records of 10th Standard Certificate or Aadhaar Card.</li>
                                                <li>Profile Photograph - Resolution of the photo should be 72 DPI with white/off white background and formal attire only.</li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </div>

                                        <div style="">
                                            2. <strong>Education & Training Details</strong> :
                                            <p>Under Education and training you need to upload.</p>
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>10th Standard Mark sheet and Certificate</li>
                                                <li>12th Standard Mark sheet and Certificate</li>
                                                <li>Diploma Mark sheet and certificate (if applicable)</li>
                                                <li>Degree Mark sheet (all semesters) and Certificate / Provisional Certificate</li>
                                                <li>PG Mark sheet and Certificate (if applicable) / Provisional Certificate</li>
                                                <li>Certificates of Certification courses (if applicable)</li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </div>
                                        <div style="">
                                            3. <strong>Identification Proofs</strong> :
                                            <p>Under Identification Section you need to upload the ID Proof documents:</p>
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>Aadhaar Card</li>
                                                <li>PAN Card</li>
                                                <li>Driving License</li>
                                                <li>Passport (Valid Copy). If you have applied for a Passport, please provide the file number along with the date of application</li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </div>
                                        <div style="">
                                            4. <strong>Work Experience</strong> :
                                            <p>Under Work Experience Section you need to upload the previous organization documents.</p>
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>Service/Experience Certificates and Relieving letters of all Previous Organizations (if applicable)</li>
                                                <li>Directorship/Partnership-Company registration document or Dissolution document (if applicable)</li>
                                                <li>For freelance/Self-employed- Experience letters, Bank Statements or Client letters (if applicable)</li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </div>
                                        <div style="">
                                            5. <strong>Health Section</strong> :
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>Under Health Section you need to upload the Fitness Certificate signed by Registered Doctor / Practitioner.</li>
                                                <li>Undertaking, if you have any health issues.</li>
                                            </ul>
                                        </div>

                                         <p>Upon completion of the Profile updating process, an auto-generated confirmation will be sent to your registered email ID. </p>
                                         <p>On your date of joining <strong>${object.tmp_join_date.strftime('%d-%b-%Y')}</strong>,
                                         it is mandatory for you to report at  Office at 10:00 AM in formal wear. You have to carry
                                         all the original certificates for hard copy verification, including the experience Letter Or
                                         Resignation acceptance letter/email from your immediate last organisation (mentioning your last working day).</p>
                                         
                                         <p>Please feel free to contact below persons, if you have any questions related to documents or need any support.</p>
                                        


                                        <br/>
                                    </div>
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                            </tbody>
                        </table>

                    </td>
                    </tr>
                    </tbody>
                </table>
	    ]]>
	  </field>
       </record>
    </data>
</odoo>