<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="bsap_terms_and_condition_page" name="Terms and Condition">
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div class="banner-navigation" style="height: 83px !important; margin-top: -41px;">
                    <div class="container">
                        <nav aria-label="breadcrumb" class="breadcrumb-Area">
                            <ol class="breadcrumb">
                                <li class="breadcrumb-item text-white">
                                    <a href="/">
                                        <i class="bi bi-house-fill"></i>
                                    </a>
                                </li>
                                <li class="breadcrumb-item active text-secondary"
                                    aria-current="page">Terms and Condition</li>
                            </ol>
                        </nav>
                    </div>
                </div>

                <div class="inner-layout">
                    <div class="about__Section--Inner">
                        <div class="container">
                            <h3 class="text-blue section__Heading">Terms and Conditions</h3>
                            <div class="table-responsive">
                                <p>
                                    By accessing this website, you agree to comply with and be bound
                                    by the following terms and conditions. Please read these terms
                                    carefully before using our website.
                                </p>

                                <h4><b>Use of Website</b></h4>

                                <p>
                                    The content of this website is for general information purposes
                                    only. It is subject to change without notice. We do not provide
                                    any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, completeness,
                                    timeliness, or suitability of the information and materials
                                    found or offered on this website for any particular purpose.
                                    Your use of any information or materials on this website is
                                    entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable.
                                </p>

                                <h4><b>Intellectual Property Rights</b></h4>

                                <p>
                                    This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to
                                    us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design,
                                    layout, look, appearance, and graphics. Reproduction of any
                                    material is prohibited other than in accordance with the
                                    copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and
                                    conditions.
                                </p>

                                <h4><b>External Links</b></h4>

                                <p>
                                    From time to time, this website may also include links to other
                                    websites. These links are provided for your convenience to
                                    provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse
                                    the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the
                                    linked website(s).
                                </p>

                                <h4><b>Changes to Terms and Conditions</b></h4>

                                <p>
                                    We reserve the right to update or modify these terms and
                                    conditions at any time without prior notice. Your continued use
                                    of the website after any changes signifies your acceptance of
                                    the modified terms and conditions.
                                </p>

                                <h4><b>Limitation of Liability</b></h4>

                                <p>
                                    In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage, including
                                    without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or
                                    any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or
                                    profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this
                                    website.
                                </p>

                                <h4><b>Governing Law</b></h4>

                                <p>
                                    Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use
                                    of the website is subject to the laws of [Your Country/Region].
                                </p>

                                <h4><b>Contact Us</b></h4>

                                <p> If you have any questions about these terms and conditions,
                                    please contact us at <a href="mailto:contact@bsap.example.com">
                                    contact@bsap.example.com</a>. </p>
                                <p>
                                    These terms and conditions were last updated on [date].
                                </p>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>